https://citysavingscu.com/privacy-policy/

Cit e-Savings Account
Daily Interest Savings Account (CDN)
Daily Interest Savings Account (U.S.)
Daily Interest Chequing/Savings Account (U.S. Funds)
Cit e-Savings Account
Daily Interest Savings Account (CDN)
Daily Interest Savings Account (U.S.)
Daily Interest Chequing/Savings Account (U.S. Funds)
Cit e-Savings Account
Daily Interest Savings Account (CDN)
Daily Interest Savings Account (U.S.)
Daily Interest Chequing/Savings Account (U.S. Funds)
Privacy Policy
Protection of Personal Information.
The following ten interrelated privacy principles are specified in the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and form the basis of the Code:
Accountability – City Savings & Credit Union is responsible for personal information under its control and shall designate a Privacy Officer who is accountable for City Savings & Credit Union’s compliance with the principles of the Code.
Identifying Purposes – The purposes for which personal information is collected shall be identified by City Savings & Credit Union at or before the time the information is collected.
Consent – The knowledge and consent of the member are required for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, except in specific circumstances as described within this Code.
Limiting Collection – The collection of personal information shall be limited to that which is necessary for the purposes identified by City Savings & Credit Union. Information shall be collected by fair and lawful means.
Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention – Personal information shall not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the member or as required by law. Personal information shall be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
Accuracy – Personal information shall be as accurate, complete, and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.
Safeguards – Personal information shall be protected by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. City Savings & Credit Union will apply the same standard of care as it applies to safeguard its own confidential information of a similar nature.
Openness – City Savings & Credit Union shall make readily available to members specific, understandable information about its policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Individual Access – Upon request, a member shall be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of their personal information, and shall be given access to that information. A member is entitled to question the accuracy and completeness of the information and have it amended as appropriate on proof of inaccuracy.
Challenging Compliance – A member shall be able to question compliance with the above principles to the Privacy Officer accountable for City Savings & Credit Union’s compliance. City Savings & Credit Union shall have policies and procedures to respond to the member’s questions and concerns.
Online Loan Application
Interac e-Transfer
Me to Me
Mobile Banking
Mobile Web Banking
Online Brokerage
Lost or Stolen Debit Card
Service Fees
Chequing/Savings (U.S. Funds)
Daily Interest Savings (CDN)
Daily Interest Savings (U.S.)
Copyright ©2019 City Savings Credit Union - Designed by Brent Bailey Internet Solutions     | Site Map | Privacy | Contact
facebook
twitter
